Guide to the Katja B. Goldman and Michael Sonnenfeldt Collection of Photographs 1900-2002 PR 305
New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Ken Regan and Camera 5, 1965-2002
  - Subseries III.1: On-Set Productions, 1970-2002
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by production title, with all featured productions identified in the container list.
    Select on-set photography, labelled according to subject, also appears in Subseries III.2.
    - All My Children [TV], circa 1985 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - Beloved, 1998 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Bridges of Madison County, 1995 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Bridges of Madison County - Laminated, 1955 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Cry Baby, 1990 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - Defection of Simas Kurdika, 1978 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Devil's Own, 1997 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3-8)
    - The Devil's Own - Laminated, 1997 (Offsite-box 25)
    - The Electric Company [TV], circa 1975 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 9)
    - The Exorcist II: The Heretic, 1997 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 10-11)
    - The Exorcist II: The Heretic - Laminated, 1997 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Freejack, 1992 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 12)
    - The Hurricane, 1999 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 13-15)
    - In the Gloaming [TV], 1997 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 16)
    - John and Mary, 1969 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 17)
    - Little Murders, 1970 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 18)
    - Look Back in Anger [TV], 1980 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 19)
    - The Molly Maguires, 1970 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 20)
    - Nell, 1994 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 21)
    - The Pelican Brief, 1992 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Philadelphia, 1993 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3-4)
    - Silence of the Lambs, 1991 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - Space Cowboys, 2000 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - The Truth About Charlie, 2002 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - A Very Special Christmas [TV], 1998 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitian Opera - Dido and Aeneas, 1973 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - The Nutcracker [TV] - Laminated, 1977 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III.2: Portraiture, 1964-1996
    This subseries represents Regan's photojournalistic reportage and trademark abilities to capture public figures in natural and intimate settings, both within and outside their professional contexts. Images cover a broad spectrum of public figures and events, and have been arranged by subject into three subseries: A) Entertainment, B) Politics and Crime, and C) Sports. All subseries are arranged alphabetically by subject. Individuals with 4-5 or more images have their own folders and entries in the container list; the others have been grouped together and are arranged alphabetically in the "miscellaneous" files. Some of the photographs have been laminated and are housed separately.
    Additional Regan portraits, including further entertainment, rock'n'roll, politics, and sports subjects, are in Series VI and VII.
    - Subseries III.2 A: Entertainment, 1964-1996
      Subseries subjects range from Classic Hollywood icons Lauren Bacall, Kirk Douglas, and Charlie Chaplin to New Hollywood stars such as Warren Beatty, Ali McGraw, Ryan O'Neal, John Travolta, Raquel Welch, Jon Voight, Ryan O'Neal, Jane Fonda, Matt Dillon, and Robert De Niro. The collection is particularly strong in newscasters and journalists: Barbara Walter, Walter Cronkite, Christine Amanpour, Phyllis George, Gay Talese, Harry Reasoner, John McLaughlin, and underwater photojournalist Peter Gimbel. A wide range of prominent directors and writers (Paul Mazursky, John Huston, A.J. Antoon, and John Houseman) theatre performers (Tyne Daly and Wooster Group founder Ron Vawter), musicians (Pearl Bailey and Neil Diamond), comedians (Bob Hope and Buddy Hackett), television stars (Gary Collins of Born Free), and New York personalities (Sylvia Miles, Celeste Holm, and "male mannequin" Kevin Boyce) are also present. Other pop culture figures featured are heiresses Gloria Vanderbilt and Ann and Charlotte Ford, Ronald Raegan's daughter Patti Davis, businessman Charles Evans, and Neil Armstrong and the Apollo 11 astronauts.
      - Dan Akroyd, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
      - Christine Amanpour, c. 1985-1995 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2)
      - A.J. Antoon, Undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
      - Alan Arkin, Undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
      - Neil Armstrong and Astronaunts, 1969 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
      - "B" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
      - Candice Bergen, Undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
      - Polly Bergen, 1980 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 7)
      - Polly Bergen - Laminated, 1980 (Offsite-box 24)
      - Ellen Burstyn, 1964-1980 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
      - Richard Burton, Undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
      - "C" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 9-10)
      - Dick Cavett and Guests, 1977, Undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 11)
      - Charlie Chaplin, 1972 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 12)
      - Gary Collins, 1974 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 13)
      - Walter Cronkite, 1981, Undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 14)
      - "D" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 15-16)
      - Patti Davis, 1983 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 17-18)
      - Matt Dillon - Laminated, 1980 (Offsite-box 24)
      - David Dukes, 1983 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
      - Robert Duvall, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
      - "E" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 16)
      - Samantha Egger, 1985 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
      - Charles Evans, 1983 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
      - "F" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 16)
      - Carrie Fisher (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
      - Ann Ford, Undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 5)
      - "G" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
      - Phyllis George, 1976 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7-8)
      - Peter Gimbel, 1981 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 9-10)
      - "H" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 10-11)
      - Gene Hackman, 1973 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 12)
      - Bob Hope, Undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 12)
      - "I" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 11)
      - Jill Ireland, 1979 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 13)
      - "J" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 11)
      - Victoria Jackson, Undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 14)
      - "K" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8-9)
      - David Keith, 1983 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 15)
      - Stacy Keach, 1984 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 15)
      - Shirley Knight, Undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 14)
      - "L" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 16)
      - Ron Liebman, 1980 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 17)
      - Joan Lunden, 1980 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1-2)
      - "M" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3-4)
      - Ali McGraw, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 5)
      - John McLaughlin, 1976 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 6)
      - Ann-Margret, Undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder 6)
      - Paul Mazursky, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 7)
      - "N" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
      - Kathy Nolan, Undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
      - "O-T" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 9)
      - Christopher Reeve, 1996 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 10)
      - John Travolta, 1978 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
      - Stanley Tucci, 1993 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 11)
      - "V" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 12)
      - Roger Vawter, 1993 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 13)
      - Jesse Ventura, 1982 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 13)
      - "W" - Miscellaneous, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 12)
      - Mike Wallace, Undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder 14)
      - Barbara Walters, Undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder 15-17)
      - "A-Z" - Miscellaneous - Laminated, 1964-1996 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Subseries III.2. B: Politics and Crime, 1966-1992
      This subseries contain portraits and candid shots of political figures. The subjects are generally New York themed or based, ranging from Bella Abzug speaking at the 1961 Womens Strike Day to the 1981 funeral of mobster Joe Columbo. The "Miscellaneous" files include activists, writers, and political figures Bill Bradley, William F. Buckley, Normal Mailer, Hugh Carey, the Prince and Princess of Denmark, Katherine Dunham, Geraldine Ferraro, Ralph Ginsburg, Robert Trent Jones, and Dennis Weaver. Subjects with their own individual files include Daniel Ellsburg (appearing on the Dick Cavett Show), Brooklyn democratic leader Meade Esposito, Watergate-implicated party John N. Mitchell, President Richard Nixon (on the campaign trail for re-election), eccentric businessman and philanthropist Stewart R. Mott, former New York City Mayor Robert F. Wagner, and an undated day-in-the-life photo shoot with inspector Joseph Fink of the New York Police Department, 9th Precinct.
      Approximately 85 photographs document politician John Lindsay (1921-2000) during his tenure as New York City Mayor (1969-1973). The materials depict Lindsay press conferences, speeches, and other event appearances, including 1971 visits to a Brooklyn swimming pool and Bronx firehouse dedication. Several files chronicle his unsuccessful 1971-1972 bid for the Democratic presidential nomination, including campaigning in Wisconsin and Arizona, and awaiting results at the primary headquarters in Tampa, Florida. Wife Mary Lindsay, civil rights activist Charles Evers, Senator Jacob Joints, President Richard Nixon and other figures, including personal staff and family are variously featured independently and with Lindsay.
      - "A-Z" - Miscellaneous, 1970-1992, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1-2)
      - Bella Abzug, 1970, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 3)
      - Joe Columbo and Family, 1978-1981, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 4)
      - Daniel Ellsburg, 1971 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 5)
      - Meade Esposito, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 6)
      - Joseph Fink, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 7)
      - John Lindsay, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1)
      - John Lindsay, 1971 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 2-3)
      - John Lindsay, 1972 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 4-5)
      - John Lindsay, Undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6-7)
      - John Lindsay with Charles Evers, Undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 8)
      - John Lindsay Family and Staff (Offsite-box 27, Folder 9)
      - John N. Mitchell, 1974 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 9)
      - Stewart R. Mott, 1979 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 8)
      - Richard Nixon, 1972, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 9)
      - Robert F. Wagner, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 10)
    - Subseries III.2 C: Sports, 1966-1983
      This subseries consists of publicity, action shots, and candids of subjects including journalist Howard Cossell, golfer Lee Trevino (appearing on The Dick Cavett Show), boxer Thomas Hearns, tennis players Bruce Jenner, gymnast Mary Lou Retton, baseball umpire Ron Luciano, and others.
      - "A-Z" - Miscellaneous, 1976-1983, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
      - "A-Z" - Miscellaneous - Laminated (Offsite-box 29)
      - Mary Lou Retton, Undated (Offsite-box 29)
  - Subseries III.3: New York Events
    This subseries features Ken Regan coverage of newsworthy events and further activity in New York City, including political rallies and protests, sporting events, local professional athletic teams, and venue interiors.
    This subseries is further divided into three subseries: A) Political Activism, B) Sporting Events and Teams, and C) Street Scenes and Interiors. Subseries III.3A, Political Activism, depicts civil rights, peace, and economic rallies and gatherings in New York City during the late 1960s and 1970s. Specific events include a Black Panthers protest of the arrest of the 'Panther 21' in Long Island City (April 6, 1970); peace demonstration outside the United Nations (April 15, 1967); and Womens Strike Day, protesting the lack of affordable or daycare centers (August 26, 1970).
    Subseries III.3B, Sporting Events and Teams, showcases action photography of athletes, behind-the-scenes personnel, and spectators, including celebrities such as John Kennedy, Sr., at New York sporting events during the late 1960s to early 1970s, with baseball, basketball, football, hockey, boxing, tennis, and horse-racing all depicted. Local professional teams the New York Giants, New York Jets, New York Knicks, New York Nets, and New York Rangers are featured, as is the 1973 United States-USSR mens basketball game and Muhammad Ali-Joe Frazier fight of June 28, 1974.
    Subseries III.3C, Street Scenes and Interiors, contains miscellaneous New York City street scenes, portraits, and interior shots.
    - Subseries III.3 A: Political Activism, 1967-1979, Undated
      - Black Panthers, 1970 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 10)
      - Rallies and Protests: Peace and Economy, 1967, 1969 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 11)
      - Rallies and Protests: Miscellaneous, 1960-1975 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 12)
      - Hair: The Musical in Central Park, Undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 13)
    - Subseries III.3 B: Sporting Events and Teams, 1968-1974
      - "A-Z" - Miscellaneous Events - Laminated, 1976; Undated (Offsite-box 29)
      - Muhammad Ali Vs. Joe Frazier, 1974 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
      - USA vs. USSR - Mens Basketball - Laminated, 1973 (Offsite-box 29)
      - New York Giants - Laminated, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 29)
      - New York Jets - Laminated, c.1968 (Offsite-box 29)
      - New York Knicks, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
      - New York Knicks - Laminated, c.1973 (Offsite-box 29)
      - New York Nets - Laminated, c.1972 (Offsite-box 29)
      - New York Rangers, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
    - Subseries III.3 C: Street Scenes and Interiors, 1970; Undated
      - Ann Cote, New York Hosptial, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
      - Fashionable Women on Fifth Avenune, 1970 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
      - Interior: The Sandwich Construction Co., World Trade Center, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
      - Interior: El Morocco, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
      - Interior: Lincoln Center, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
  - Subseries III.4: Dachau
    This sub-series features undated photographs taken of memorials, exhibitions, and visitors of Dachau, the site of the first Nazi concentration camp in Germany. The pictures are undated but taken some time after 1965, when the former camp was opened to the public as a memorial and museum.
    - Dachau, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5-6)
- Series IV: 2015 Accruals, 1958-1995
  This series consists of material donated by Katja B. Goldman and Michael Sonnenfeldt in 2015. It includes photographs by Jill Freedman, Fred McDarrah, and Ken Regan and Camera 5.
  The series is arranged into subseries by photographer, and each subseries is arranged by subject.
  - Subseries IV.1: Jill Freedman, 1969-1986
    This subseries contains documentary photographer Jill Freedman's work focusing on New York City police, firefighters, and street scenes.
    This subseries is arranged by subject
    - Firefighters and Police Officers, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1-2)
      images of New York City firefighters and police officers on the job, from Freedman's books "Firehouse" (1977) and "Street Cops" (1981).
    - New York City Scenes, 1969-1986 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 3-5)
      includes images of the Brooklyn Bridge; Central Park; Feast of San Gennaro; Greenwich Village; parades; people in costumes; people on the street; Soho; street musicians and performers.
  - Subseries IV.2: Fred McDarrah, 1958-1995
    This subseries contains the work of Village Voice photojournalist Fred McDarrah. During his 50-year career at the Voice, McDarrah documented the galleries, lofts, cafes, bars and streets of Greenwich Village and Soho, and the artists, musicians, Beat poets, and writers who populated them. Included are photos of Allen Ginsberg, Jack Kerouac, Edward Hopper, Willem de Kooning, John Lennon and Yoko Ono, Sly Stone, Patti Smith, Hugh Carey, and John Lindsay, among many others. Also included are images of Act-Up demonstrations, Gay Pride marches, sit-ins, and the Woodstock music festival.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Actors, 1972, undated (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1)
      Susan Anspach; Fred Astaire; Warren Beatty; Ellen Burstyn; Dyan Cannon; Marilyn Chambers; Candy Darling; Brad Davis; Robert De Niro; Gene Kelly; Ben Kingsley; Roy Rogers; Jimmy Stewart; Meryl Streep; Donald Sutherland; Elizabeth Taylor; Lily Tomlin; Liv Ulmann; Jennifer Warren; Leslie Ann Warren; Sigourney Weaver
    - Artists, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 2)
      Tony Smith (sculptor)
      Hans Hoffman (painter)
      Edward Hopper (painter)
      Willem de Kooning (painter)
    - Events, 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3-4)
      ACT-UP demonstrations; Democratic National Convention NYC; Gay Pride/Stonewall Anniversary demonstrations; NAMES Project AIDS Memorial Quilt display; Police negotiating a hostage crisis in a bank; Watkins Glen Music Festival; Welfare Sit-in; Woodstock
    - Musicians, 1974-1975, undated (Offsite-box 33, Folder 5)
      John Lennon and Yoko Ono with Simon and Garfunkel and Roberta Flack; Diana Ross; Patti Smith; Sly Stone; Barbra Streisand; Sarah Vaughn; Mary Lou Williams (jazz pianist); Stevie Wonder
    - New York City Scenes, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 6-7)
      Bars and taverns, including the Lion's Head and Costello's; the Dakota; the Garment District; Soho, including the E.V. Haughwourt building, the Little Singer building, and the 1971 opening of an art gallery at 420 Broadway; the subway; Times Square; Washington Square Park; construction site of World Trade Center; abandoned buildings and urban blight; newstands, traffic, street art fairs, street life.
    - Politicians, 1968-1972, undated (Offsite-box 33, Folder 8)
      Hugh Carey; Hubert Humphrey; Robert F. Kennedy's funeral; Ted Kennedy; John V. Lindsay; George McGovern; Arthur Schlesinger; Robert F. Wagner.
    - Writers, 1958-1995, undated (Offsite-box 33, Folder 9)
      Allen Ginsberg; Barbara Guest (poet); Molly Haskell and Andrew Sarris (film critics); Jack Kerouac; Norman Mailer; Also includes images related to the Beat literary scene: a rack of Beat poetry books, closing night of the Beat hangout the Cedar Street Tavern, and photos of the "Beatnik presidential candidate," and "Miss Beatnik of 1959."
  - Subseries IV.3: Ken Regan and Camera 5, 1964-1989
    This subseries contains the work of photojournalist Ken Regan and Camera 5, the photo agency he founded to cover wars, riots and demonstrations, and other national and international hard news and human interest stories. Regan worked for over five decades documenting pop culture, celebrities, sports, foreign conflicts, and other current events.
    This subseries is organized into six further subseries, arranged alphabetically by subject:
    Subseries IV.3 A: Events
    Subseries IV.3 B: Film, Music and Theater
    Subseries IV.3 C: News Broadcasting
    Subseries IV.3 D: Political Figures
    Subseries IV.3 E: Sports
    Subseries IV.3 F: Sports Figures
    - Subseries IV.3 A: Events, 1969-1973
      includes photographs of a parade honoring returning Vietnam veterans; Dancer Sally Rand performing at the Museum of the City of New York (Rand donated the fans from her fan dance performance at the 1939 World's Fair to MCNY); a Republican Party dinner at the Waldorf Astoria; and restauranteur Toots Shor's 70th birthday party.
      - Home With Honor Parade, 1973 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1)
        images for a parade held for returning Vietnam War veterans in New York City.
      - Sally Rand fan dance performance at the Museum of the City of New York, 1969 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 2)
      - Republican party dinner at the Waldorf Astoria, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 3)
      - Toots Shor's 70th Birthday party, 1973 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 3)
    - Subseries IV.3 B: Film, Music, and Theater, 1967-1983
      This subseries includes images of film and stage actors, directors, producers, and critics, as well as musicians.
      - A.J. Antoon, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 4)
      - Joe Papp, 1971, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 5)
        includes images of Shakespeare in the Park
      - Arthur Penn, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 6)
      - Peter, Paul and Mary, 1967 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
      - Tony Randall, 1970 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 8)
      - Rex Reed, circa 1970 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
      - Susan Sarandon, 1981 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
      - Jonathan Schwartz, 1980 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 9)
      - Maxim Shostakovich, 1969 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 10)
      - Helen Slater, 1983 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
      - Anna and Lee Strasberg, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 11)
      - Gay Talese, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
    - Subseries IV.3 C: News Broadcasting, 1974-1981
      This subseries consists of images of television news broadcasters, journalists, and reporters on and off set. Includes the sets of ABC News, the Today Show, Good Night America, and CBS Morning News. Features photos of news personalities Tom Brokaw, Walter Cronkite, Jane Pauley, Sally Quinn, Dan Rather, Harry Reasoner, Geraldo Rivera, Jessica Savitch, and Liz Smith.
      - Geraldo Rivera, 1974 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 12)
      - Television News, 1980-1981, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 13)
        Images of television news broadcasters on and off set. Includes the sets of ABC News, CBS Morning News, the Today Show, and Good Night America. Features photos of news personalities Tom Brokaw, Walter Cronkite, Jane Pauley, Sally Quinn, Dan Rather, Harry Reasoner, Jessica Savitch, and Liz Smith.
    - Subseries IV.3 D: Political Figures, 1964-1989
      This subseries features photographs of the Kennedy family; David and Nelson Rockefeller; activist turned businessman Jerry Rubin; feminist leader Gloria Steinem; and U.S. ambassador Sichan Siv.
      - Kennedy Family, 1964-1981 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 14)
        includes images from Robert F. Kennedy's funeral train.
      - David Rockefeller, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 15)
      - Nelson Rockefeller, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 15)
      - Jerry Rubin, 1980 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 16)
      - Sichan Siv, 1989 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 17)
      - Gloria Steinem, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 18)
    - Subseries IV.3 E: Sports, 1960-1983
      This subseries features images of athletes and fans at sporting events, icluding baseball, boating and sailing, boxing, football, horse racing, karate and squash. Photographs of the New York Mets and New York Yankees baseball teams make up the bulk of this subseries.
      - Baseball - New York Mets, 1966-1983 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 1-5)
        images of Mets players on the field, in the dugout and the clubhouse. Team members pictured include manager Casey Stengel, Cleon Jones, Tom Seaver, Ron Swoboda, and Jerry Koosman, Ed Kranepool, and Marv Thornberry. There are also images from the Mets' 1969 World Series victory, as well as photos of Mets fans in the stands.
      - Baseball - New York Yankees, undated (Offsite-box 35, Folder 6)
      - Boating and Sailing, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 7)
      - Boxing, 1960 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 8)
      - Football, 1968, undated (Offsite-box 35, Folder 9)
      - Horse racing, 1966-1981 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 10)
      - Karate, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 11)
      - Squash, 1970 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 11)
    - Subseries IV.3 F: Sports Figures, 1966-1974
      This subseries consists of photographs of sports figures on and off the playing field. Included are basketball player Wilt Chamberlain, bull rider Bobby Del Vecchio, football player Dick Lynch, swimmer Diana Nyad, and chess player Boris Spassky.